Rockville Journal World War II Letters
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Hirth, Warren C, undated; Walla Walla,WA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hirth, Warren C, undated; Salt Lake City, UT; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hirth, Warren C, undated; Great Bend,KS; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hirth, Warren C, undated; FortGeorgeWright,WA; Spokane,WA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hirth, Clarence, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hirth, Theodore A, undated; Camp Beale; CA; Discharged, Miltary Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hlasney, Joseph G, undated; Kasselo; Germany; with Enclosure Stars and Sripes; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hlasney, Joseph G, undated; Kasselo; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hlasney, Joseph G, undated; Camp Stewart; GA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hlasny, Joseph G, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Co F 311th infantry; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hoague, Earl, undated; Stafford Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hodelski, Vincent, undated; Mrs Ralph Wilcox; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hoffman, Robert P, undated; South Wellfleet; MA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hoffman, Robert P, undated; Texas A & M College; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hoffman, Earl, undated; Main Street; Broad Brook; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Holland, Robert N, undated; Trudx Field; Madison, WI; Graduated from Radio Mechanics School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Camp San Luis Abispo,CA; City Life; San Francisco,CA; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; England; D Day; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Syracuse University; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Vernon; NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; University of Illinois; IL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Fort Totten,NY; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Camp San Luis Abispo,CA; City Life; Golden Gate Bridge; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Camp Carson,CO; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Fort Bragg,NC; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Los Angeles,CA; US Army; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Champaigne,IL; US Army; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Los Angeles,CA; US Army; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Champaigne,IL; USO; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Camp Stoneman,CA; USO; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Camp San Luis Abispo,CA; USO; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; Camp Stoneman,CA; USO; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopkins, Edwin W, undated; New York,NY; On Furlough; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hopowiec, Chester M, undated; Lake Placid; NY; Returned, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Howard, Chester E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Camp Dauis,NC; Advance Course Antiaircraft Artillery School; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hunniford, William Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed in Action,18,Guam; Son of Mr&Mrs Wm John Hunniford,Village; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hunniford, William Jr, undated; Mrs Bernice Hunniford; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hunniford, William J, undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edward R, undated; Philippines; with Japanese Occupation Money; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edward R, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edward R, undated; Santa Ana; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edward R, undated; New Bern; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edward R, undated; New Bern; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edward R, undated; New Bern; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edwin R, undated; Cherry Point; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Edwin R, undated; Cherry Point; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Hyjek, Rudolph, undated; Navy War Casualties Report - Wounded; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Irmischer, Oscar E, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Irmischer, Oscar E, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Irmischer, Oscar E, undated; Charleston; SC; Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jacewicz, Stanley F, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jackopsic, John A,Jr, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jacobs, Horace, undated; MacDill Field,FL; Pinup; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jacobs, Horace, undated; 9th Air Force Bomber Base; France; Keeping Runways Clear of Snow; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jahne, John S, undated; 5th Army; Italy; Battle History of Unit; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jaikey, Francis, undated; Martinsburg; WV; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jaikey, Francis, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jakapic, Paul, undated; Fort Knox, KY; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jakapic, Paul, undated; Fort Knox; KY; Completed Basic Training; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jalbert, Norman M, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Pacific,Submarine Duty; Son of Mrs Alma Jalbert,17 Windsor Avenue; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janicki, Stella, undated; Corpus Christi; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jankanskas, Stanley J, undated; 15th Armay; Germany; History of 569th Field Artillery Battalion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; Walter Beeck Gen Hospital; Washington, DC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; Camp Hulen,TX; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; England; City Life; Buckfast Abbey Church; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; Washington,DC; City Life; Supreme Court Building; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; Camp Hulen,TX; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 113 Brooklyn Street; 2 Edward Jantons; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, Edward, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 2 Edward Jantons; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, John J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed in Action,25,Germ; Nephew of Mrs Victoria Janton,Brooklyn St; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Janton, John J., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jarazynski, John, undated; Puunene, Maui; HI; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jasion, Chester, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jasion, Francis S, undated; Butler; Pacific; Convalesing After Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jelinek, Norman E, undated; US Naval Prison; Portsmouth, NH; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jelinek, Norman E, undated; FPO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, George H, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, George H, undated; France; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Harold F, undated; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Harold F, undated; Japan; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Wallace Jr, undated; Rosecrans Field; St Joseph, MO; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Wallace Jr, undated; St Joseph,MO; Scenery; Rosecrans Field; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, George H, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Wallace Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, George H, undated; Mrs George H Johndrow; Discharged,Military Record; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Wallace Jr, undated; Rosecrans Field; St Joseph, MO; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johndrow, Wallace Jr, undated; Rosecrans Field; St Joseph, MO; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johnson, William B, undated; San Antonio; TX; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johnson, Rev Adolph, undated; Fort Trumbull,CT; US Maritime Service; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Johnson, Philip E, undated; Amston; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jones, Roland C, undated; Corsica; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jones, Walter C, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jones, Walter C, undated; Apo New York City; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Jones, Walter C, undated; England; History of USA Army Ordnance Battalion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, Harold L, undated; Apo New York City; Ny; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, James L, undated; Sampson; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, James L, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, James L, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, James L, undated; Chicago,IL; City Life; University of Chicago; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, Harold L, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 108 Union Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Joyce, Harold L, undated; Mrs Minnie Joyce; Service Update; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; Lafayette; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; Dutch East Indies; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; Maxwell Field,AL; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; 5th Air Force; Southwest Pacific; Joined Jolly Rogers of 5th Air Force; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; 5th Air Force; Philippines; Arrived in Philippines; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Judge, Alfred J Jr, undated; Far East Air Force; Philippines; Received Award; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder Di-J)
  - Kadelski, Joseph W, undated; Rockville; CT; With Description of Service; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Joseph W, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Matthew, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Stephen, undated; Newport; RI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Stephen, undated; Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Vincent, undated; Pueblo; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Vincent, undated; Peublo,CO; Camp Life; Army Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kadelski, Joseph W, undated; Fort Ord, CA; Camp Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kahan, Robert F, undated; Fort jackson; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kaminski, John A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Killed Camp Lejeune,NC; Son of Mr and Mrs Frank KaminskiAge 46; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kaminsky, John A., undated; Vernon; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Karkevich, Peter A, undated; Italy; Promotion, Military Record; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Karkevich, Peter A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Karkevich, Peter A, undated; Italy; Served Engineer Unit with Rockville Men; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kauppi, Jerome F, undated; Clemson; SC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kauppi, Jerome F, undated; Greensboro; NC; Arrived for Basic Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kawalec, John, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kawalec, Stanley F, undated; Greensboro; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kayan, Steven P, undated; San Francisco; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kayan, Steven P, undated; Port Hueneme,CA; City Life; Wichita,KS; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kayan, Steven P, undated; Midway Islands; Location and Background; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Keeney, Raymond, undated; Died in Plane Crash; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Keeping, Douglas L, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Keller, Edward A, undated; Turin; Italy; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Keller, Edward A, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Keller, Edward A, undated; 5th Army; Italy; Returning Home; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kelley, Arthur, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; Killed Camp Gruber, OK; Son of Mr and Mrs Bernard Kelley,Age 27; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kelley, Lionel B, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kellner, Earl L, undated; Seymour; IN; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kellner, Earl L, undated; Bowling Green; KY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kellner, Earl L, undated; San Antonio; TX; Receiving Flight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kellner, Earl L, undated; Scott Field; IL; Training as a Radio Technician; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kellner, Erich A, undated; 8th Air Force; On List of 8th AF after VE Day; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kemble, Lester R, undated; US Air Force; England; Received Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kemble, Lester R, undated; Air Force; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kemble, Lester R, undated; Air Force; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Ketcham, Stephen E, undated; Selma Field; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Ketcham, Stephen E, undated; Selma Field; LA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Ketcham, Stephen, undated; Moody Field,GA; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Ketcham, Stephen E, undated; Smyrna,TN; Air Force; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Ketcham, Stephen E, undated; Murfreesboro,TN; City Life; Middle Tennessee State College; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Ketcham, Stephen E, undated; Selman Field; Monroe, LA; Commissioned as Aerial Navigator; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kibbe, Edward W, undated; New Address, Mae Varish; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kibbe, Edward W, undated; Ellington Honor Roll; West Road; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kibbie, Edward W, undated; Fort Bragg,NC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - King, Robert J, undated; Panama City; FL; Graduated from Air Force Gunnery School; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - King, Robert J, undated; Keesler Field; Biloxi, MS; Reported for Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kington, Ellery G, undated; Indiantown Gap; PA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kington, Ellery G, undated; Paris,France; City Life; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kington, Ellery G, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kiss, Charles, undated; Italy; History of Aviation Engineer Battalion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kita, Theophilus, undated; Fort Lewis,WA; Scenery; Mount Rainier; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kita, Theophilus, undated; Fort Lewis,WA; Scenery; Mount Rainier and Girls; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kitra, Theophilus, undated; Camp Sibert,AL; Scenery; Noccalula Falls,Gasden,AL; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klecak, Joseph H, undated; Connecticut; Connecticut Soldiers in Service; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; Cambridge; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Vernon C, undated; Lake Geneva,NY; Scenery; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; Maxwell Field,AL; Souvenir Folder; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Military Record; Press Release-Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Vernon C, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Description of Military Service; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; England; Combat Event; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klette, Immanuel J, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Edward G, undated; New Guinea; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Edward G, undated; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Wilbur B, undated; APO NYC; NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Noel R, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Winfred, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Noel R, undated; Mrs Noel Kloter; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Noel R, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Noel R, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Noel R, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kloter, Noel R, undated; 8th Air Force; England; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Klute, Donald H, undated; Guam; Working in Jungle Hospital; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knebel, Stanley, undated; Fort Totten; Long Island NY; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knebel, Stanley, undated; Tyndall Field; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knebel, Stanley, undated; Tyndall Field,FL; War Bonds; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knebel, Stanley, undated; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knight, Clifford, undated; Camp Blanding; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knight, Clifford B Jr, undated; England; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knight, Clifford B,Jr, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Frank, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Joseph, undated; Camp San Luis Obispo; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Joseph, undated; Camp Gruber; OK; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Joseph, undated; Camp Gruber; OK; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Michael E, undated; Philippines; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Michael E, undated; Honolulu; HI; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Michael E, undated; South Pacific; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Walter W, undated; India; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Walter W, undated; India/Burma; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Frank, undated; Camp Pickett; VA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Joseph, undated; Camp Gruber,OK; Camp Life; Fort Gibson Stockade; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Walter W, undated; Greensboro,NC; Humor; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Michael, undated; Sampson NY; Finished Training,On Leave; Press Release-Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Frank, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Son od Mr&Mrs John Knybel,Snipsic Lake RD; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Knybel, Walter W, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; 33 Brooklyn Street; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koblect, Lawrence M, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Completed Field, Wireman Course; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koblect, Lawrence M, undated; Fort Dix; NJ; Assigned to 9th Infantry Division; Military (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kocher, Willaim W, undated; Italy; City Life; Palermo; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koehler, Leon R, undated; Tolland Honor Roll; Welcome Home Pgm; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koehler, Leon R, undated; Italy; Awarded Medal, Military Record; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koehler, Leon R, undated; Italy; Promotion; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koehler, Leon R, undated; Italy; Served Engineer Unit with Rockville Men; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kollar, Bohumil E, undated; 2nd Infantry; Germany; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kollar, Bohumil E, undated; 2nd Infantry; Germany; Battle Description; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kolodezak, Nicholas, undated; Kingman; AZ; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kolodezak, Nicholas, undated; Greensboro; NC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kolodezak, Nicholas, undated; Boca Raton; FL; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kolodezak, Nicholas, undated; Mrs T Borovicka; New Address; Press Release-Family (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koschwitz, Alexander H, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Koschwitz, Carl F, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kowal, Edward, undated; NYC; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kowalczwk, Henry A, undated; Luzon; Philippines; Arrived in Philippines; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kowaleski, Joseph, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photo in Phillipines; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kowaleski, Joseph, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; See Edward Berriault; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kowalski, John S, undated; San Antonio; TX; Undergoing Preflight Training; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kozlowski, Chester, undated; Vernon Honor Roll; Photograph (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Krajewski, Herman A, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Krajewski, Herman A, undated; APO San Francisco; CA; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Krajewski, Herman A, undated; Camp Edwards,MA; City Life; White River Junction,VT; Postcards (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Krajewsky, John S, undated; Germany; Letters (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)
  - Kramer, John L, undated; Austria; Awarded Medal; Press Release (Box Cabinet 1, Folder K-M)